We will start off our BBQ tour in Austin.
Iron Works, then to Rudys, then to Lamberts.
We will then take 183 South to Lockhart.
And visit Smittys, Kreuz Market,
and Blacks Smokehouse.
And I assume we'll start the day at Franklin BBQ.
My Leader...
It...
It is too late to go to Franklins.
It is already past 10:30 AM.
Anyone who has not been to Franklins.
Please,
Leave the room.
30 minutes before they open!
Too late! 30 minutes before they open!
Who do these pit bosses think they are?
Oooo their brisket is so special!
We were late last time,
All they had left was cole slaw.
All I hear from everyone,
"Oh Franklins is so amazing, you have to go!"
Sir, we told you to get there early.
Early?  Not a whole entire hour early!
Sir, you said it can't be that good.
That was until I saw 150 people in line.
Ridiculous!
People camped all night once,
Just to be first in line.
Just to get a cheap cut of beef!
How are the rest of us
supposed to compete with that?
Just to get a decent lunch.
I do profess it is simply unfair!
These waiting lines are like living under Stalin.
They think they are so special.
Sure, there are never more
than 5 people at Bananarchy.
Even during ACL.
It just seems like,
I'll never get to eat BBQ there.
To be forever tormented by everyone asking me,
"Isn't Franklins the BEST?"
To which I can only sheepishly respond,
"Yes! The cole slaw is amazing!"
Gerda, you'll get to go there someday.
All I wanted was a quarter lb of moist brisket.
A couple of pork ribs would be a nice addition too.
A sausage link.
Some espresso sauce.
Instead I'll be eating BBQ from a gas station.
Or what I dread most,
Salt Lick.